In the first match of Group B, the
first ball of this over from bowler Omkar Pavilion was a good ball, it hit the legs
but signaled leg bye,
so welcome once again umpire Mr. Om Singh
to our com box, that
means batting, you have batted as well as
bowled and this time you have played your over,
excellent shot, powerful, brilliant four runs,
you have played cricket, season, leather, everything, you have
also done umpiring, you
just have to come to the commentary box.
Right?
Yes Ritesh, after listening to your commentary, I also feel like saying the same thing, though
I may
not be able to say it like you, but I will
definitely try.   A
very directionless ball,
not umpire Tajmul, he says with effort and hard work, here
one says that you will get success one
day and the same has happened for the last
four years, yes he has
played it over the fielder, the ball is going
out of the boundary line for four runs, powerful,
brilliant and a four, lions in the jungles,
peacocks in the gardens, the batsman has hit a brilliant
four,
thank you, thank you, thank you,
we Bengalis, we will say onek onek,
both are very nice,
Mitesh, it is 12:00 and now you have started writing
poetry, the
next ball was a good ball from Omkar, it was
on the feet but the batsmen stole a run by playing it on the square leg.   Yes,
absolutely, here people steal hearts
but players steal runs.   Yes,
Amitesh
and this directionless ball is of Omkar.
12 runs have been scored in four balls of the first over
or the start has been very good.  I think
this is the magic of double breakfast.  Om Sir,
yes
and we
should also thank the organizing committee that the
batsmen are batting here after eating the kind of breakfast that is required.   Yes,
I have packed the parcel secretly.  He bowled the
last ball of this over
and wanted to hit a shot but the fine leg
fielder
and Sushant Patil made a good start.
Te Patan sa bullock cart, kitni karna rada one was gone
14 for no loss Infina
strikers, it was a very expensive over for Omkar. The
next bowler Satyam
Leather is a professional bowler in cricket and
also bowls tennis well.  Satyam is a left arm bowler.
Is this S for Satyam?  S for Special
Satyam.   Yes.
I have umpired many of his matches.
And
last year also
I got the opportunity to umpire this ICC tournament
and I am fortunate that this year also
I have been given the responsibility of umpiring.
Absolutely and in combobox you have instant
booking.  Right?  [Music] Yes.   Got the
ticket immediately.  Satyendra Singh, a
very experienced
bowler, has come to bowl.
And look at this, this is the reason the experience
contender is called for
todi na why na why book in stumps
why?  That's clean bowled gone.
What a start This is from Satyendra
Singh
The Timber Shattered and the Dream Scattered
First Wicket Fall Infina Strikers
14 for One 1.1 [Music]
So a timely break through.  Has made a
comeback.  Yes, as I have
already told you that Satyam is a good bowler
and I am telling both the teams that it is a five
over match and two bowlers can bowl two overs each.
One bowler per over means
you can use three bowlers.   Yes, there
is definitely an option that you can use two bowlers
for two overs.  So I
think we will definitely give two overs to Satyan.   Yes,
Satyam has definitely won the heart of his captain. He took a wicket on the first ball and the second
ball was a dot. The third ball of this over was a very
good ball in the block hole. The batsman could
not understand and wanted to play on the on side but was
completely beaten.
This is the wonder of bowling. If
you play cricket with a leather ball, then even with a tennis ball,
it impresses the batsman and
Satyan has made a similar start.  Yes,
if you read the batsman, your
ball will definitely go well.  Satyam saw the
batsman stepping out a little and bowling the ball
at his feet.  Next ball from Satyam.   It was a
very good ball.  It hit the feet.   There was a
huge appeal there and
what a jump the keeper made.
Very good decision by both the umpires.   The
edge of the bat was taken.  Look, the keeper
also
tried very well but one bounce
came in his hand.
You cannot escape the umpire's eyes.   right back at Ya.
Professionalism.
The Professional Umpires We Have.
This was also a good ball.  Towards fine leg.
So see how the placement
of the tennis ball is, seeing the placement here is a very rare
situation.  When there is a
bowler like Satyendra Singh, there is terror.  There was
an atmosphere of fear.  Now yes,
one run was given in five balls.  One
ball left sir.  One ball left.
One ball remaining.  Wow good bowling.
Last ball of this over of Satyam
and again he batted, again he batted,
wow good bowling, once again a big applause for
Satya Singh,
only one run and one wicket and in the first over
Om sir 14 runs came and this is a comeback.
Yes, Omkar's over was very expensive which has been
filled and taken out.  Satyam bowled
two overs, 15 runs, two wickets.
Yes, Tajmul sir, please tell the bowler to bowl a little faster. The
match is not fast. They are not there, the match is full.
Our
bowler Shubham has bowled
his team.
Power play has started. Five players can be kept out.
Shubham took a
wide wicket. First, the
score is 16 runs.
Second, the
batsman was
playing on the on side.
One attack solved the problem. This
over was bowled by two runs. Two overs, two runs. Two balls,
17 runs.
Shubham Changli was bowling. This
over had four runs.
Two overs, four runs.
One wicket.
Very unlucky number. Right, danger on 17. It could have happened
here,
but
luck was on his side.
Top edge and went towards the backward region
for four runs.
With this four runs, Anuj Shah took
the first boundary and Amol Pawar took the
second wicket. 2.5 21 for one. Infina
Strikers are
very excited. Proud Warriors team
Howden
and the start they made.  The Proud Warriors would have
blown the speaker if they had a microphone.  Om
sir.
Hello hello, yes Mitesh sir, the way the
batting team started with 14 runs,
I think it could have been a much bigger score
Mitesh, but
Shubhan and Satyam bowled very well.
Yes, if we talk about it, in the last two overs, only
eight runs have been given and one wicket has been taken.   Yes.
So this is Restricted now
Infina Strikers for a big score.
Once again Satyam has
come to bowl the second over.  It remains to be seen
what the batsmen do in this over and to what extent Satyam is
able to stop them.
He gave only one run in the first over.
Left arm round wicket from Satyam towards the pavilion,
very good ball but
wants to pull it towards mid wicket, there is a fielder down there
but the fielder could not stop it and the ball
went for four runs or that's excellent
shot, a bit of misjudgement by the fielder but
good attempt, one bounce into the fence for four
runs,
Anu Shah is batting well with four runs.  Om Sir
10 of 8 vs two Force.   Yes.   There
is a big responsibility on them.  Can make a comeback in the match.   Yes.
We will compensate for whatever loss has occurred.   Yes,
Mitesh Satyam's [music] next ball.
Four runs came off the first ball.
And it
is very difficult to kill this Satyam.  Block Hall had the ball.   Yes,
absolutely excellent bowling.  He says,
tola in a moment, masha in a moment, Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham,
who will become the Singham of the match,
this and the fall of one wicket, he was
completely beaten, Anuj Shah ji was batting
and gone, second wicket fall of Infina
Strikers 3.2, 26 for 2, it has become a
very quick game, Om Sir,
yes
and the most interesting thing when we used to watch ODI was that we used to
watch the first 15 overs, then we used to switch
off the television set and watch the last 40 to 50
overs by turning on the television, yes, yes,
that era was something different, that's how all of us
viewers used to watch, telecast at home, live
telecast,
cricket has become so craze now that
every parent wants that my son should be like Sachin
and Virat, very good bowling
and this and one wicket,
Sachin was beaten,
I think S for special S for Satya
and S for Saturday, Saturday special Satyan
Singh ji, yes,
bowling very carefully, Satyam
definitely gave four runs in the first ball, but
what a comeback, then two wickets in two balls,
or now Satyendra is on a hat-trick
Singh
26 per three 3.3
Infina Strikers Both teams have made a good
start.
On a hat-trick, Satyendra Singh,
excellent bowling, tap and play only
a single here,
meaning you can imagine the spectators watching,
how would you bowl in tennis ball or season ball,
you
bowl very well, in season ball
he bowls with left arm over
but in tennis he bowls with left off round
and this time a good strike would
go for two runs in the long off area but the
throw is excellent but if it was
needed directly on the stump then the wicket could have been taken,
3.5 on 29, three infina strikers
in the next seven balls, Om Sir, I think it is
important to cross that 40 mark.
Going for another run.  There's a
throw in at the striker's end but I think the keeper was a
bit late.   Could
not collect.  Is
it out on the stumps?   Yes, it is
run out.  The umpire took some time
but that's run out and gone.
Excellent throw there by Dipesh
four overs 30 for four Infina Strikers
Excellent bowling spell from Satyendra
Singh Two no for three
something they restricted and let's see now
last over coming up of the first innings
change in the field settings
excellent bowling wow a good pace delivery but they will go
for two as a
long distance and umpire
singling no ball that's a fielding
restriction
it was kept to be four fielders inside the
circle
but there were three fielders
and that's the golden opportunity to go
for some big hits.
Oh that's good bowling from Kaushik
33 for four last five balls coming up.  You are
watching ICICI Lombard Presents
Brokers Premier League Two to Six Season
Three and this is Group B match one
om
and here and a wicket is taken here in the form of a run out.
So Alien Strikers really good fielding
but also good batting from Infin
Strikers.
Good throw from Prasad
4.335
for five last three balls first innings
very good bowling but the
ball went a little outside the off stump line with
that x extra 36 for five last
three balls
swing in miss that's a very good bowling
chance for the run out at the non-striker
and but sent back by the striker batter
36 for five
last two balls
wow good bling this be chance for the run out o they are
going for one more run o in
fact they were looking for one more run three runs two
runs taken capitalise on two runs 38 for five
last ball
last ball the first innings will they go for
big hits and will all strikers will
take a wicket
that's out no runs at the last ball so five
overs 38 for six and 39 to win for all
strikers
and a request for the toss time
for next next match
captain of Pran Warriors come.  Pran
Warriors and Team Howden For the Coin
Warriors Captain and Team Howden Captain I
request you to come on the center stage of the
ground.
Prudent Warriors Captain The
sky is blue Your jersey is also blue
Who will make it loose Who will have to watch
I request the team How done come yes we have How done
Captain Vishal and Prudent
vs Captain Ashish First of all How is the
feeling Ashish Quite exciting Quite exciting
and we are very much
thrilled to play again and this very good
tournament organized by S Lambat and
will definitely try to win this again
ok I wish you all the best and now How done How is
the feeling First match will be played against
Prudent Warriors They have a
strong batsman Mangesh Jagtap You must be
knowing that at least three sixes, four sixes
in every innings Last match I remember Prudent
Warriors they played 15 sixes in one innings
in six overs in Australia There was a
short ground but this is a big distance
ground What would you like to say No it's been
great Firstly I would like to thank
ICSCI alumnus for giving us this
Opportunity to play well we know that
student is a brilliant team ah so we will
look forward for a great competition and we will
disappoint the crowd so biggest rival
coming up right ok so Kapil sir joining
for the coin toss who will call how done will
call heads is a call
tails it is you won the toss what will you
take first and why to?  Want to ball
first.  ah because as he is directly
mentioned this is a very I mean big ah
boundaries as a compare to the last to
last edition.  And we've played last
edition it is we want to chase this target
whatever target how done will set for us.
and Letts C.  All the best to How Dan.  So,
how done team ah how much target will you
give them?
Well let's see now.  ah will this be the first match
we are playing so we will also need to
assess ah the wicket?  Ah who is the playing 11 how does it
work?  So let's see hopefully will
give a good target.
I wish you all the best Team Howden and here goes
Captain.  It is not a big thing.
So match number two of Group B coming up
Prudent Warriors won the toss decided to
bowl first.
Hello Hello First match of Group B
39 runs in 5 overs
First ball straight drive Fielder present Have to be
satisfied with one run
Rishi on strike
Both the batsmen play from the same team.
Leather
Satyam has bowled very well.   It remains to be
seen what contribution Rishi makes for his team.
Rishi is known to be a very long hitter. It
was a good ball. [Music] Off side
and this is a
no ball signal.
Fielding destruction.
You have to keep only two players out.  Only
two players have to be kept out in the first two overs.
Captain, please pay
attention.
So Om Sir, it is easy to play tennis cricket in this ground
because the leather ball travels.
Yes,
and the wicket is very hard
and the
leather ball is the match I was playing yesterday, the target was 202 runs
on the same wicket,
but there is a lot of difference between tennis and leather.   The
next ball was hit into the lock hole on the feet
but could not stop the batsman from scoring a run.
Great effort by the bowler.  Gaurav Maskar is bowling
himself completely on the pitch,
Satyendra
Singh is batting and Rishikesh is bowling,
three balls of this over are
five runs
and Satyam hit the fielder and Satyam took a very
good catch,
well taken, there excellent catch, good judgment
and that's a wicket number one of All
Strikers, a good bowling from Gaurav, they were
definitely looking for a wicket,
bowling by Gaurav, catch also taken by Gaurav,
if the match is going to be
strong, Gaurav
four balls, five runs, one wicket, Alliance
Strikers,
the equation is 26 balls and 34 runs up the
over, just for the fielder, there the fielder is
standing at mid-wicket
for a single, next two overs
if the team Infina Strikers bowl economically, they
give only 10 runs in the next two overs, it might be a little
difficult, then Allan Strikers have to
win this match, chase 39 runs, full
toss ball, hit it well,
fielder is present at mid-off, only one run will be taken here,
one was gone from for one  24 balls left and
32 runs they need to win this match.  Who will become a
magician?  Who will be called the conqueror of destiny?
Stay tuned to watch ICCIC
presents Brokers Premier League Two and
Two Six.  Season Three
16 Teams for the One Glory We have the two
teams from the Group A stage.  Admit
Idence and Pink Panthers into the quarter-
finals.  The same
playing style in Group B is seen in Group C as
well as Group D.
So all the league's matches in the day one and
from day two will have the quarter finals from
quarter finals to final finals.
That's between the fielders
safe no run
Deepesh and Rishikesh
change in the field setting deep extra cover
is now shot extra cover mid off wide
mid on mid off you can say got that
inside edge lucky and good bowling
from Gaurav
one more Gaurav in the attack
after Gaurav Musker Gaurav God
and that's the free twenty.
Gifting run, five run
is available here, rub the sandalwood of the free, my
son,
five run here, the score with extras
is 13 off 16, 26 runs are needed in 3.4 overs,
now L Strikers will
keep this match in their strong grip, there
is a chance of run out here but the keeper could
not hit the stumps.
14 for one with the single 25
now for the left hand there is a fielder at
mid wicket cow corner.
No fielder standing at square leg.
And that's a good strike at long on
region Anuj the fielder just a single that's a
clever bowling a bit of bowling
very variation from Gaurav and completely
beat and batsman looking to play across the
line
only seven runs given in this over
six runs in the first over Gaurav Maskar now Gaurav God
down the track a bit of in the air but safe and
single to the end of the over so two overs gone 16
for one
23 runs in 18 balls 23 runs in 18 balls
and here to beat the heat we have thanda thanda cool cool
lemonade
two overs 16 for one 23 runs in 18 balls
fielding change
fielder is stationed at deep backward point shot third man fine leg
shot cover
one fielder at wast long off one at long on one at
cow corner one ad mid wicket
that's a field setup from the team Infina
Strikers will have to
see in this coming over Infina
Strikers if they can able to defend this
target giving  Not many runs
to the team Airline Strikers
Anuj Shah
left arm over the wicket for the left hander
o that's very clever bowling the batsman
thought going outside the off line but no just
pitching inside the line
and this is what Infina Strikers Anuj
Shah
will look something special in this world will try to
take wicket
excellent bowling looking for a big one miss it
completely only one
run considered three balls that's what we are
talking about that coming two overs not
giving many runs in finish Strikers can make a
comeback in the match.
Correct bowling here by Anushka
once again swing in miss o was there an
outside edge
it looks like that was edged behind the
stumps and the wicket keeper has put it down.   That's why that was
disappointment on the
face of Anuj Shah.
He has given only one run in four balls.  One fielder at deep backward square
leg, one at cow corner for the left-hander.
Once again.  Wow good bowling.  What a beauty
of a delivery.
Just one run in five balls.
He reminds me of Wasim Akram.
What a great swing king
Wasim Akram was in that era.
This time it has been played down the track from above.
But proper fielding there, only two runs were
conceded.
Can we have a big round of loss for Anuj
Shah
very interesting performance on
18 after three overs
need 21 runs in another two overs 21
om om om om
very crucial over of the match but going down
the leg side wide.
18 runs from 11 balls.
Umpire took some time going just outside the
line for wide
now from 11
in this over infinite strikers and eleven
strikers who will
get the match on
very good bowling
excellent bowling
not allowing the batter to go for some big hits
that was very well left by the batter just
going to on the leg side for wide
15 runs needed in 10 balls and this time
which government
and this is a chance.  Looks like this time it's
Infinity Strikers' government.  People are
saying something or the other government.  I would say this
time only a government of cricket.
This could be the game.  A game-changing moment
for the team Infin Strikers.
Excellent catch taken by Anuj
bowled really well now also in the fielding
side once again a good strike hit hard
just a single
14 runs and eight balls
will Rishikesh
send the ball into the Mumbai skylines
oh that's very good bowling dot ball
seven balls left and 14 to get what a
match excellent performance from both the teams
toss delivery and check gone captain has taken that
catch amazingly done, made a splash
batting team is in
trouble and one wicket has fallen
now 14 runs are needed in six balls we have to see
whose government will be in power stay tune to watch
ICC Sem Brokes Premier League Two to
Six Season 3
our Om Sir is saying the commentator has made us
happy.
What would you like to say Om Sir?  This match has been very
interesting.  14 runs off six balls.
Hello, yes Mitesh, nothing can be said in cricket.
Currently it is running at 60 40%.  The fielding team has
60% of the game left now.  But Omkar
is also a well-known batsman who has
played a lot of tennis cricket.
And he bowled the best.
Two runs in one over.  Anuj is back.   Yes.
Oh, here was the opportunity.  There was a chance but I missed it
and Omkar also had a chance on this ball to
play on the leg side, the ball was a short one
but the bat hit the top edge,
yes absolutely, every chance that comes here should be
grabbed,
13 runs were needed in five balls,
wanted to play by creating space but the
ball was going outside the leg stump and with one extra at the right time,
12 runs were needed in five balls.   Will we
see a big head from Prasad in the next two balls?
Oh, there could have been a
chance of run out here but
only a single could have been taken for two runs
because at such times they say, keep
adding straw to whatever you get, let it fly, even if your
life is lost for someone, we are
just moving on the path of cricket,
adding straw to straw, they say, drop
by drop creates trouble.
Ball in the air but no man's land, two runs will be
taken here
and we will have to see what comes next. Now nine runs in three balls,
a big hit,
Onkar Prasad,
big responsibility.
Very crucial ball of the match coming up,
three balls have been played at nine runs,
space has been created but the fielder will
not be able to catch it there, there is a
twist in the story.  What has
happened?  How did it happen?  It was a miracle.  The magic happened.
So beautiful, so elegant looking like
a wow.
Om Sir, you are absolutely right that anything can happen.
Anything can be anything.
I know Omkar very well.
He is known for his long hits.
Three runs are needed in two balls and
Anuj Shah will try to take a wicket here.   I have
played this time.  The ball is going
over the fielder and out of the boundary line, four
runs.
This is Omkar's batting.  I told you Mitesh
that he can do anything in the match.
Absolutely Sir and I would like to say Mausam Mastana
Rasta Anjaana Alliance Strikers have made
everyone crazy.